{
    "subject": "resource/The_Last_Legion",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Ben_Kingsley",
    "human_readable": "The Last Legion stars Ben Kingsley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6916176676750183,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5109432339668274,
            "question": "Name an actor who appears in The Last Legion."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46196073293685913,
            "question": "Who directed The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44335731863975525,
            "question": "What genre of film is The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44194692373275757,
            "question": "Which movie features Ben Kingsley as a main character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4342699348926544,
            "question": "In what movie does Ben Kingsley have a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4267660677433014,
            "question": "What film is Ben Kingsley known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40847882628440857,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Ben Kingsley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3376248776912689,
            "question": "List some actors who have worked with Ben Kingsley."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19931180775165558,
            "question": "Is Ben Kingsley in any movies about ancient Rome?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Last Legion stars Ben Kingsley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8372_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=List some actors who have worked with Ben Kingsley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8372_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film featuring Ben Kingsley?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8372_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is Ben Kingsley known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8372_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8372_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"It stars Colin Firth, Ben Kingsley, Aishwarya Rai...\" and \"...the cast includes Colin Firth along with Sir Ben Kingsley and Aishwarya Rai.\" This suggests that the statement \"The Last Legion stars Ben Kingsley\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents confirm that Ben Kingsley is one of the stars in the film \"The Last Legion.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}